

CTO Technopreneur Developer Educator



elixirdose.com



github.com/rizafahmi



medium.com/@rizafahmi22



https://id.linkedin.com/in/rizafahmi

A mad computer scientist who enjoy managing geeks and developers since 2011, more than 13 years of successful experience in programming web, mobile applications, and databases. Became curriculum director at Hacktiv8 in a mission to changes other's live and provides awesome talents to the country.

My specialty is trying crazy ideas and getting them to work.

Experiences

Hacktiv8

Curriculum Director 03/2016 - now

Responsible for all aspect of curriculum for 12 weeks immersive coding bootcamp, teach and mentoring students. Guiding curriculum and instructor team to provide students with the supportive environment and outstanding material.

CitizenLab.co

Chief Technology Officer 08/2015 - 01/2016

I'm in charge on all aspect of technological side in CitizenLab. Doing back-end most of the time, front-end a little bit, maintenance code, infrastructure, architecture, and such.

HarukaEdu

Software Developer - R&D 07/2013 - 09/2015 (2 years 3 months)

Develop the platform using PHP and MySQL. Creating Development Plan. Managing Project and Developer Team. Development, and maintenance the platform. Did R&D for platform improvements.

Education

University of Indonesia

Magister in Information Technology 2008 - 2010

Master thesis : Model Knowledge Management System For Internal Helpdesk.

Bina Nusantara University

Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology 1999 - 2003

Languages

English, Indonesia (Native)

Projects

Hakctiv8: Immersive Coding Bootcamp AppsCoast: Indonesian Tech Startup Podcast BdB Audio News Technical Proofer "Elixir In Action" Book ElixirDose Blog

Tools

VIM/NVIM
iTerm2
Slack
*nix/Linux
MindNode
Evernote
Dash

xcode

Dev Skills

Python
NodeJS
PHP
Blixir/Erlang
Obj-C/Swift
PostgreSQL
MongoDB
Docker

Hobbies









